### **MERVE TAFRALI**



I am a fourth year student in the Department of Computer Engineering at Kocaeli University. In 2019, I worked as a long term trainee at Netaş. I was working in the defense department about voip and some java applications. In the summer of 2018, I did my internship in Kordsa's global IT department. I worked on c# and mvc technologies in my internship. I did an internship for 2 years as a volunteer in the school department lab. I took 3 academic publications on image processing and did the work on wordpress at Kocaeli University Laboratory of Embedded Systems.

### **Personal Information**

Address:	Körfez/KOCAELİ
Telephone :	0545 799 48 43
E-mail:	mervetafralii@gmail.com
Gender :	Female
Birth Date :	23.12.1996
Marital Status :	Single
Driving Licence:	B(2015)

### **Education Informations**

	Kocaeli University Faculty of Engineering Computer Engineering 2016-2020 General Percent Average:3.08/4.00
09/2010-06/2014	Derince Anatolian High School 2010-2014 General Percent Average: 68.12/100

## Languages

	Writing	Reading	Speaking
English	Advanced	Advanced	Intermediate

# Job Experiences

01/12/2016 -08/08/2018	Intern at Embedded System Laboratory in Kocaeli University  Articles in image processing Applications in java Wordpress designer	
13/08/2018-18/09/2018	Intern at KORDSA Global It Department Supplier Management Website working with asp.net-MVC	
24/01/2019-01/06/2019	Long term intern at NETAŞ- Defense Department  VolP and Java application	

## Software Knowledge

<ol> <li>Python- Intermediate</li> <li>Java - Intermediate</li> <li>SQL - Intermediate</li> <li>A</li> </ol>	Spring-Maven-Hibernate - Intermadiate Asp.net,MVC- Intermadiate Html,css,js- Intermadiate Android- Intermadiate Angular.js,Node.js,React,Ionic-Intermadiate
--	---

# Projects

<ul> <li>Hotel Tracking System, Java</li> <li>Book Suggestion and Reading Application c#</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>News Website, Java, Hibernate, Spring</li> <li>Smart Advertising, Android Java</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Supplier Management Website</li> </ul>	You can see all my projects: https://github.com/mervetafrali

### **COURSES and CERTIFICATES**

- Object Oriented Programming , Java Development- Elginkan- (72 Hours)
- ❖ Project development with Spring + Hibernate + JSP + Maven Udemy
- ❖ C # Programming Tutorial -Udemy
- ❖ American Life-English language education-up to the level c2

### **Social Activities**

Online Games, e-Sports, Book reading, Swimming, travel, writing

### **Articles**

- Object Detection and Segmentation on Apple Tree Images by Using Morphological Operations and Vertical and Horizontal Histogram Values
- ❖ Wound Edge Detection Operation Using Enhanced Canny Edge Detection Algorithm on Dermatological Images
- ❖ The Enhancement of Canny Edge Detection Algorithm Using Prewitt, Robert and Sobel Kernels

### References

Caner İhtiyar Technology Manager in KORDSA caner.ihtiyar@kordsa.com 0505 922 09 24